# **KEYUR PATEL**

## FULL STACK DEVELOPER

**\** +1 (408) 506 7277

ttps://github.com/ekeyur

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ekeyur

#### **PROFILE**

I have over 5 years of management consulting, 2 years of product management experience and I have been developing full Stack projects for over 6 months. I am currently seeking opportunities where I can put my skills to good use and improve my problemsolving abilities. I have a love for learning new skills, and enjoy working on teams.

#### **EDUCATION**

### DigitalCrafts

SEPT 2016 - JAN 2017 Certificate Full Stack Development

#### **Georgia Institute of Technology**

AUG 2003 - JULY 2007 Bachelor of Science Industrial Engineering (Optimization)

SKILLS

**NODE.JS** 

IONIC **POSTGRESQL** CSS MONGODB **JAVASCRIPT GITHUB ANGULARIS JOUERY** 

MEAN **EXPRESS PYTHON VUE.JS** 

BOOTSTRAP FLASK

# HOBBIES

Reading | Running | Biking | Ping Pong

TDD (JASMINE)

### **EXPERIENCE**

### Digital Crafts, Developer in Residence

SEPT 2016 - PRESENT

#### AirNavAtl: An app to navigate inside of Atlanta airport

- Created using Python, AngularJS, PostGreSQL & Leaflet API
- Used Dijkstra's algorithm to find the shortest path
- Mainly contributed in backend and api generation
- Demo available at: https://airnavatl.com

#### TripGoalie: An app to facilitate safe travel on MARTA

- Participated in a 24 hour MARTA hosted hackathon for nonprofits
- Developed using Python, Flask, Jinja 2 and PostGreSQL
- Designed and developed complete backend with one other developer
- Demo available at: http://tripgoalie.com

#### Fabulari: Speech modeling app for kids with disabilities

- Developed using AngularJS, MongoDB, Express and Node.js
- Contributed to database schema design and backend APIs and helped build AngularJS logic on the front end
- Demo available at: http://fabulari.org

#### **Grillber: A rental service for Big Green Eggs**

- Developed using Python, Flask, Jinja 2 and PostGreSQL
- Contributed to database schema design, backend logic and implemented stripe
- Demo available at: http://grillber.com

# Realization, Product Manager / Strategy Consultant

SEPT 2008 - SEPT 2016

#### Product Manager, Concerto (2014 - 2016)

- Responsible for coming up with new features to be developed
- Created user stories and prioritized development queues
- Interfaced with UI/UX designers for wireframes and design approval
- Interfaced with stakeholders to gather requirements and the direction of the product
- Created user stories for developers and snippets on product updates for marketing
- Created product demos for use in the field for sales team

#### Management Strategy Consultant (2008 - 2014)

- Developed and implemented strategies and processes to improve project deliveries in multiple industries
- Trained consultants on data gathering, data analysis and client investigations on site
- Accompanied sales directors to answer any technical questions on the product